DONNY PHAN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

■ donthephan@gmail.com ♦ https://donthephan.com ♦ 6478182780 ♥ Toronto, Canada in donnyphanmeceng/ ♠ donthephan

SUMMARY

A Full-Stack Web Developer with 9 years of experience in Mechanical Design and Project Management. Experience with PERN Stack - Front End in React, HTML, CSS & JavaScript, and Back End in Node.js, Express & PostgreSQL. Open to Relocation.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: Javascript, Python, HTML & CSS, SQL, Git

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES: React, NextJS, Node.js, Express, Bootstrap, jQuery, Tailwind CSS, Sass

TESTING: Debugging, Jest, Mocha & Chai, Cypress, Storybook, Postman **OTHER:** RESTful API, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, WebSockets, Figma, Canva

PROJECTS

StoryTime

TECH USED: React, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, Tailwind CSS, Daisy UI, Git/GitHub, Socket.io, RESTful API, Netlify, Heroku, Figma and Trello.

- Mobile first, StoryTime connects readers with people who want to be read to.
- Team project using Agile practices with daily scrum meetings.
- Responsible for Wireframing, Front End Design and Implementation, Webchat and Back End Web Hosting.

E-Commerse Store

TECH USED: React, Node.js, Material UI, Firebase, Git & GitHub

- Interface connects to Paypal.
- · Responsive Design.

Path Finder

TECH USED: React, Node.js, Firebase, Git & GitHub

- Grid Path Finder instantly finds the shortest path using path finding algorithms Dijkstra's and A*.
- Features auto generating maze algorithm, users can draw their own obstacles, and responsive design.

Interview Scheduler

TECH USED: React, Storybook, Cypress, Jest, API and Git/GitHub.

- Books, cancels and makes changes to interview bookings.
- Unit Testing.

EDUCATION

University of Toronto

BASc Mechanical Engineering Degree

Lighthouse Labs

Diploma Full Stack Development

Academind

Certificate React|s

The App Brewery Nov. 2020 to Mar. 2021

Certificate Computer Programming in Python

EMPLOYMENT

Spec Furniture

Mechanical Designer

Toronto, Ontario July 2016 to June 2020

Sept. 2004 to May 2008

Nov. 2021 to Feb. 2022

June 2021 to Aug. 2021

- Initiated and scripted drawing tools to reduce design times, up to 90% reduction (60 min to 5 min).
- Trained new Designers to use AutoCAD, SolidEdge, and understand furniture industry standards.
- Consulted clients, helping them understand their needs while mitigating issues in design/production.

Array Marketing

Project Manager Assistant

Scarborough, Ontario May 2013 to July 2016

• Managed 2-3 teams of 4-5 members each, developing, producing and delivering Cosmetic Displays to 400+ stores world wide.